flashbuzz.info 2016-03-20

# Privacy – FlashBuzz.info

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for [www.flashbuzz.info](http://www.flashbuzz.info/). This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site. It will notify you of the following:

  1. What personally identifiable information is collected from you through the web site, how it is used and with whom it may be shared.

  2. What choices are available to you regarding the use of your data.

  3. The security procedures in place to protect the misuse of your information.

  4. How you can correct any inaccuracies in the information.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are providing curated content/information on this site for entertainment purposes only. We only have access to collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address given on our website:

• See what data we have about you, if any.

• Change/correct any data we have about you.

• Have us delete any data we have about you.

• Express any concern you have about our use of your data.

**Cookies**  
We may use “cookies” on this site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a site visitor’s hard drive to help us improve your access to our site and identify repeat visitors to our site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information on our site.

Some of our business partners may use cookies on our site (for example, advertisers). However, we have no access to or control over these cookies.

**Sharing**  
We may share aggregated demographic information with our partners and advertisers. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. However, we have no control over third party websites once you exit our website.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

**If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately via admin@flashbuzz.info**
